{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.457747, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a089f170-7085-11ea-822f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b44da-7085-11ea-8654-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b45b6-7085-11ea-9fa4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "When will this end ?", "answerText": "This is a difficult question , because a lot depends on how well the virus is contained . In places including China , Singapore , South Korea and Taiwan , fierce efforts to contain the virus appear to have reduced the number of new cases . In the United States , forecasts differ depending on where you live . New York City , Seattle , Boston and parts of California already have such large outbreaks that they will probably see significant growth even after taking extraordinary preventive measures , according to Columbia University researchers who used a New York Times database and Census Bureau data to model outcomes . Some experts have guessed , optimistically , that the virus could abate in about two months , although that does not mean that public life would go back to normal . The more we take early precautions to protect our communities , like practicing social distancing , the better the results will be . If measures to slow the disease are n\u2019t effective , the virus could sicken millions of people , losing steam on the coasts in May before spreading to the rest of the country over the summer . Clinical trials for vaccines are underway in the United States , China and Europe . But American officials and pharmaceutical executives have said that a vaccine remains at least 12 to 18 months away .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "When will this end ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "This is a difficult question , because a lot depends on how well the virus is contained . In places including China , Singapore , South Korea and Taiwan , fierce efforts to contain the virus appear to have reduced the number of new cases . In the United States , forecasts differ depending on where you live . New York City , Seattle , Boston and parts of California already have such large outbreaks that they will probably see significant growth even after taking extraordinary preventive measures , according to Columbia University researchers who used a New York Times database and Census Bureau data to model outcomes . Some experts have guessed , optimistically , that the virus could abate in about two months , although that does not mean that public life would go back to normal . The more we take early precautions to protect our communities , like practicing social distancing , the better the results will be . If measures to slow the disease are n\u2019t effective , the virus could sicken millions of people , losing steam on the coasts in May before spreading to the rest of the country over the summer . Clinical trials for vaccines are underway in the United States , China and Europe . But American officials and pharmaceutical executives have said that a vaccine remains at least 12 to 18 months away .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466507, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b478c-7085-11ea-96cf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b47d2-7085-11ea-b1d9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4806-7085-11ea-a993-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I help ?", "answerText": "Charity Navigator , which evaluates charities using a numbers - based system , has a running list of nonprofits working in communities affected by the outbreak . You can give blood through the American Red Cross , and World Central Kitchen has stepped in to distribute meals in major cities . More than 30,000 coronavirus - related GoFundMe fund - raisers have started in the past few weeks . ( The sheer number of fund - raisers means more of them are likely to fail to meet their goal , though . ) Read More                You can find more relief organizations and ways to give here .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I help ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Charity Navigator , which evaluates charities using a numbers - based system , has a running list of nonprofits working in communities affected by the outbreak . You can give blood through the American Red Cross , and World Central Kitchen has stepped in to distribute meals in major cities . More than 30,000 coronavirus - related GoFundMe fund - raisers have started in the past few weeks . ( The sheer number of fund - raisers means more of them are likely to fail to meet their goal , though . ) Read More               You can find more relief organizations and ways to give here .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4665291, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4854-7085-11ea-a514-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4886-7085-11ea-be7a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b48b8-7085-11ea-9927-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I get help ?", "answerText": "This is a fast - moving crisis , and the social , medical and economic fallout is going to affect millions of people for months to come . There are many places you can go for help , whether you need relief from bills or are worried about becoming sick . There \u2019s a lot of information below about specific situations . Here \u2019s a quick guide to some of the big ones that might be on your mind . Read More                Here \u2019s what to do if you or a loved one might be sick . Here \u2019s what \u2019s in the U.S. stimulus package to help Americans . Here \u2019s how to get help with your bills .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I get help ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "This is a fast - moving crisis , and the social , medical and economic fallout is going to affect millions of people for months to come . There are many places you can go for help , whether you need relief from bills or are worried about becoming sick . There \u2019s a lot of information below about specific situations . Here \u2019s a quick guide to some of the big ones that might be on your mind . Read More               Here \u2019s what to do if you or a loved one might be sick . Here \u2019s what \u2019s in the U.S. stimulus package to help Americans . Here \u2019s how to get help with your bills .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4665458, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b48fe-7085-11ea-9abb-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4930-7085-11ea-92c5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4962-7085-11ea-80f3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Help me understand the economic fallout .", "answerText": "It \u2019s felt a lot like 2008 , has n\u2019t it ? Peter S. Goodman , an economics correspondent for The Times , says there \u2019s a key difference between that economic turmoil and today \u2019s : the utter unpredictability of the outbreak \u2019s spread . \u201c The disaster feels eerily familiar , with trillions of dollars in wealth annihilated near - daily and deepening fears that businesses will fail , \u201d he writes . \u201c Yet the traditional policy prescriptions seem no match for the affliction at hand . \u201d The very means of controlling the health crisis \u2014 keeping workers home , limiting travel and disrupting commerce \u2014 risk making the economic crisis worse . \u201c A sense of powerlessness is feeding the fear that is prompting investors to dump anything risky , which is in turn damaging economic prospects and reinforcing fear \u2014 a feedback loop , \u201d he writes . Read MoreRead Peter S. Goodman \u2019s full story here .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Help me understand the economic fallout .", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "It \u2019s felt a lot like 2008 , has n\u2019t it ? Peter S. Goodman , an economics correspondent for The Times , says there \u2019s a key difference between that economic turmoil and today \u2019s : the utter unpredictability of the outbreak \u2019s spread . \u201c The disaster feels eerily familiar , with trillions of dollars in wealth annihilated near - daily and deepening fears that businesses will fail , \u201d he writes . \u201c Yet the traditional policy prescriptions seem no match for the affliction at hand . \u201dThe very means of controlling the health crisis \u2014 keeping workers home , limiting travel and disrupting commerce \u2014 risk making the economic crisis worse . \u201c A sense of powerlessness is feeding the fear that is prompting investors to dump anything risky , which is in turn damaging economic prospects and reinforcing fear \u2014 a feedback loop , \u201d he writes . Read MoreRead Peter S. Goodman \u2019s full story here .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4665642, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b49b4-7085-11ea-aab9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b49e4-7085-11ea-afaf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4a0c-7085-11ea-99b4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I heard that Americans were getting checks . What \u2019s that about ?", "answerText": "With the $ 2 trillion stimulus legislation passed by Congress on March 27 , federal lawmakers agreed to provide $ 1,200 in direct payments to millions of Americans , including those incomes up to $ 75,000 per year . Families would receive an additional $ 500 per child . These aspects of the aid plan are attempts to create a safety net for those whose jobs and businesses are affected by the pandemic . Read MoreHere \u2019s how those checks would work .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I heard that Americans were getting checks . What \u2019s that about ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "With the $ 2 trillion stimulus legislation passed by Congress on March 27 , federal lawmakers agreed to provide $ 1,200 in direct payments to millions of Americans , including those incomes up to $ 75,000 per year . Families would receive an additional $ 500 per child . These aspects of the aid plan are attempts to create a safety net for those whose jobs and businesses are affected by the pandemic . Read MoreHere \u2019s how those checks would work .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466582, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4a70-7085-11ea-8cf5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4aa2-7085-11ea-8b8e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4ad4-7085-11ea-8f97-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does unemployment insurance work ?", "answerText": "The stimulus plan includes a significant expansion of unemployment benefits that would extend jobless insurance by 13 weeks . The program is aimed to help freelancers , part - time workers , furloughed employees and gig workers , such as Uber drivers , as well as full - time employees who have lost their jobs . States have set their own rules for eligibility and benefits , which are generally calculated as a percentage of your income over the past year , up to a certain maximum . Some states are more generous than others , but unemployment typically replaces about 45 percent of your lost income . Under the plan , eligible workers would get an extra $ 600 per week on top of their state benefit . One important note : You might not have to lose your job to qualify . If you \u2019re quarantined or have been furloughed \u2014 and you \u2019re not being paid but expect to return to your job eventually \u2014 you may be able to get unemployment benefits . Read MoreHere \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does unemployment insurance work ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The stimulus plan includes a significant expansion of unemployment benefits that would extend jobless insurance by 13 weeks . The program is aimed to help freelancers , part - time workers , furloughed employees and gig workers , such as Uber drivers , as well as full - time employees who have lost their jobs . States have set their own rules for eligibility and benefits , which are generally calculated as a percentage of your income over the past year , up to a certain maximum . Some states are more generous than others , but unemployment typically replaces about 45 percent of your lost income . Under the plan , eligible workers would get an extra $ 600 per week on top of their state benefit . One important note : You might not have to lose your job to qualify . If you \u2019re quarantined or have been furloughed \u2014 and you \u2019re not being paid but expect to return to your job eventually \u2014 you may be able to get unemployment benefits . Read MoreHere \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466599, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4b1a-7085-11ea-85c9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4b42-7085-11ea-ba89-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4b74-7085-11ea-a518-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I \u2019 m having trouble paying my bills . What can I do ?", "answerText": "Student loans The Department of Education has granted a payment waiver of at least 60 days to many people . But it \u2019s not necessarily automatic . In general , you have to call your loan servicer to request a waiver and to make sure that your loan is eligible . The waiver does not apply to private student loans . One big private lender , Sallie Mae , said it is offering suspension of payment for up to three months , with no damage to a borrower \u2019s credit . With the stimulus package , there will be automatic payment suspensions for any student loan held by the federal government until Sept. 30 . It may be hard to contact many of the loan servicers right now , so check your account online in the coming weeks . Utility bills Some utility providers are offering to stop cutting people off for nonpayment . A number of large internet companies have agreed not to terminate residential or small - business customers who ca n\u2019t pay their bills . Exact policies and requirements vary , though , so if you need help , you should call and ask . Housing There \u2019s also a good chance you can delay your mortgage payment if the outbreak has left you short of money . The Federal Housing Finance Agency has instructed mortgage servicers to allow borrowers whose mortgages are owned by Fannie Mae or Freddie Mac to delay payments . If you rent , the best national resource we \u2019 ve found so far is the search - by - state function on Justshelter.org . This offers information on local organizations that can provide advice to renters in distress . Loans and credit Many consumer lenders are offering affected customers help if they ca n\u2019t make payments . The American Bankers Association has a list of lenders here , although the help they \u2019re offering varies . Some say they will allow borrowers to skip payments ; some are offering other accommodations . Read MoreHere \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I \u2019m having trouble paying my bills . What can I do ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Student loans The Department of Education has granted a payment waiver of at least 60 days to many people . But it \u2019s not necessarily automatic . In general , you have to call your loan servicer to request a waiver and to make sure that your loan is eligible . The waiver does not apply to private student loans . One big private lender , Sallie Mae , said it is offering suspension of payment for up to three months , with no damage to a borrower \u2019s credit . With the stimulus package , there will be automatic payment suspensions for any student loan held by the federal government until Sept. 30 . It may be hard to contact many of the loan servicers right now , so check your account online in the coming weeks . Utility bills Some utility providers are offering to stop cutting people off for nonpayment . A number of large internet companies have agreed not to terminate residential or small - business customers who ca n\u2019t pay their bills . Exact policies and requirements vary , though , so if you need help , you should call and ask . Housing There \u2019s also a good chance you can delay your mortgage payment if the outbreak has left you short of money . The Federal Housing Finance Agency has instructed mortgage servicers to allow borrowers whose mortgages are owned by Fannie Mae or Freddie Mac to delay payments . If you rent , the best national resource we \u2019ve found so far is the search - by - state function on Justshelter.org . This offers information on local organizations that can provide advice to renters in distress . Loans and credit Many consumer lenders are offering affected customers help if they ca n\u2019t make payments . The American Bankers Association has a list of lenders here , although the help they \u2019re offering varies . Some say they will allow borrowers to skip payments ; some are offering other accommodations . Read MoreHere \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4666162, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4bba-7085-11ea-a86b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4bec-7085-11ea-8b9f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4c14-7085-11ea-944b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do with my 401(k ) ?", "answerText": "Watching your balance go up and down can be scary . You may be wondering if you should decrease your contributions \u2014 do n\u2019t ! In fact , if your employer matches any part of your contributions , make sure you \u2019re at least saving as much as you can to get that \u201c free money . \u201d Many components of the stimulus package , passed on March 27 , include changes to rules regarding retirement account withdrawals , borrowing and penalties . Read More                Learn more about how the stimulus package has crtchanges to retirement accounts with the stimulus package .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do with my 401(k ) ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Watching your balance go up and down can be scary . You may be wondering if you should decrease your contributions \u2014 do n\u2019t ! In fact , if your employer matches any part of your contributions , make sure you \u2019re at least saving as much as you can to get that \u201c free money . \u201d Many components of the stimulus package , passed on March 27 , include changes to rules regarding retirement account withdrawals , borrowing and penalties . Read More               Learn more about how the stimulus package has crtchanges to retirement accounts with the stimulus package .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466631, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4c50-7085-11ea-a9a0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4c82-7085-11ea-9ec7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4cb4-7085-11ea-af6d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I be putting my money in a mattress ?", "answerText": "That \u2019s not a good idea . Even if you \u2019re retired , having a balanced portfolio of stocks and bonds so that your money keeps up with inflation , or even grows , makes sense . But you may want to think about having enough cash to cover basic needs if you \u2019re retired . One financial planner recommended that retirees set aside enough cash for a year \u2019s worth of living expenses and big payments needed over the next five years . Read More                Here \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I be putting my money in a mattress ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "That \u2019s not a good idea . Even if you \u2019re retired , having a balanced portfolio of stocks and bonds so that your money keeps up with inflation , or even grows , makes sense . But you may want to think about having enough cash to cover basic needs if you \u2019re retired . One financial planner recommended that retirees set aside enough cash for a year \u2019s worth of living expenses and big payments needed over the next five years . Read More               Here \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466648, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4cfa-7085-11ea-b17e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4d2c-7085-11ea-a9d9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4d54-7085-11ea-a800-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I refinance my mortgage ?", "answerText": "It could be a good idea , but lenders are overwhelmed right now , so expect the process of shopping and closing to take time . When mortgage rates fall to record lows , as we \u2019 ve seen in recent weeks , refinancing can be a good way to save some extra cash or to shorten your loan term and pay it off faster . If you shorten your loan term to 15 years from 30 years , your monthly payments are likely to rise , but you \u2019ll have more flexibility in your budget sooner than you would \u2019 ve had . Read More                Here \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I refinance my mortgage ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "It could be a good idea , but lenders are overwhelmed right now , so expect the process of shopping and closing to take time . When mortgage rates fall to record lows , as we \u2019ve seen in recent weeks , refinancing can be a good way to save some extra cash or to shorten your loan term and pay it off faster . If you shorten your loan term to 15 years from 30 years , your monthly payments are likely to rise , but you \u2019ll have more flexibility in your budget sooner than you would \u2019ve had . Read More               Here \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466665, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4da4-7085-11ea-b996-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4dcc-7085-11ea-ba3b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4dfe-7085-11ea-8997-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What do I do about my taxes ?", "answerText": "The United States has moved the federal tax - filing deadline to July 15 , giving Americans an additional three months to file their income tax returns . Some states are also making changes . The American Institute of Certified Public Accountants is tracking those on its website . Read More                Here \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What do I do about my taxes ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The United States has moved the federal tax - filing deadline to July 15 , giving Americans an additional three months to file their income tax returns . Some states are also making changes . The American Institute of Certified Public Accountants is tracking those on its website . Read More               Here \u2019s how the outbreak can affect your personal finances .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466683, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4e58-7085-11ea-a97d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4e8a-7085-11ea-bf60-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4eb4-7085-11ea-b286-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Will I be paid if I \u2019 m told to stay home ?", "answerText": "A coronavirus emergency relief package , passed by Congress in mid - March , gives qualified workers two weeks of paid sick leave if they are ill , quarantined or seeking a diagnosis or preventive care for the coronavirus , or if they are caring for sick family members . It gives 12 weeks of paid leave to people caring for children whose schools are closed or whose child care provider is unavailable because of the coronavirus . Many workers at small and midsize companies and nonprofits can get the paid leave , as can government employees , as long as they \u2019 ve been employed at least 30 days . The law includes people who do n\u2019t typically get such benefits , like part - time and gig economy workers . But it excludes those at companies with more than 500 people , including many front - line employees at many major retailers and fast - food restaurants . Workers at places with fewer than 50 employees are included , but the Labor Department could exempt small businesses if providing leave would put them out of business . Employers can also decline to give leave to workers on the front lines of the crisis : health care providers and emergency responders . Read MoreWho qualifies for paid leave under the new coronavirus law .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Will I be paid if I \u2019m told to stay home ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "A coronavirus emergency relief package , passed by Congress in mid - March , gives qualified workers two weeks of paid sick leave if they are ill , quarantined or seeking a diagnosis or preventive care for the coronavirus , or if they are caring for sick family members . It gives 12 weeks of paid leave to people caring for children whose schools are closed or whose child care provider is unavailable because of the coronavirus . Many workers at small and midsize companies and nonprofits can get the paid leave , as can government employees , as long as they \u2019ve been employed at least 30 days . The law includes people who do n\u2019t typically get such benefits , like part - time and gig economy workers . But it excludes those at companies with more than 500 people , including many front - line employees at many major retailers and fast - food restaurants . Workers at places with fewer than 50 employees are included , but the Labor Department could exempt small businesses if providing leave would put them out of business . Employers can also decline to give leave to workers on the front lines of the crisis : health care providers and emergency responders . Read MoreWho qualifies for paid leave under the new coronavirus law .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4667, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4ef8-7085-11ea-a85d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4f28-7085-11ea-a807-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4f5c-7085-11ea-a3c4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How worried should I be about getting sick ?", "answerText": "Everyone should be concerned about contracting the new coronavirus \u2014 if not for yourself , then to protect others who are at risk of becoming severely ill . As with the flu , the virus is more dangerous for people who are older than 60 , people who have a weakened immune system , and people with an underlying condition , like diabetes , asthma or another chronic illness .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How worried should I be about getting sick ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Everyone should be concerned about contracting the new coronavirus \u2014 if not for yourself , then to protect others who are at risk of becoming severely ill . As with the flu , the virus is more dangerous for people who are older than 60 , people who have a weakened immune system , and people with an underlying condition , like diabetes , asthma or another chronic illness .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4667149, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b4f98-7085-11ea-8b0c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b4fca-7085-11ea-a75d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b4ff4-7085-11ea-8a82-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are the symptoms of the coronavirus ?", "answerText": "Common symptoms include fever , a dry cough , fatigue and difficulty breathing or shortness of breath . Some of these symptoms overlap with those of the flu , making detection difficult , but runny noses and stuffy sinuses are less common . Some people have also reported losing their sense of smell . Most people fall ill five to seven days after exposure , but symptoms may appear in as few as two days or as many as 14 days . Read MoreHere are the symptoms to look out for .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are the symptoms of the coronavirus ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Common symptoms include fever , a dry cough , fatigue and difficulty breathing or shortness of breath . Some of these symptoms overlap with those of the flu , making detection difficult , but runny noses and stuffy sinuses are less common . Some people have also reported losing their sense of smell . Most people fall ill five to seven days after exposure , but symptoms may appear in as few as two days or as many as 14 days . Read MoreHere are the symptoms to look out for .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4667299, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b502e-7085-11ea-8b5e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5062-7085-11ea-88ca-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5088-7085-11ea-90ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What should I do if I feel sick ?", "answerText": "If you \u2019 ve been exposed to the coronavirus or think you have , and have a fever or symptoms like a cough or difficulty breathing , call a doctor . They should give you advice on how to get tested and how to seek medical treatment without potentially infecting or exposing others . The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says that if you \u2019re sick or think you \u2019re sick , but only mildly ill , you should isolate yourself , and you should n\u2019t leave your house except to go to the doctor .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What should I do if I feel sick ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "If you \u2019ve been exposed to the coronavirus or think you have , and have a fever or symptoms like a cough or difficulty breathing , call a doctor . They should give you advice on how to get tested and how to seek medical treatment without potentially infecting or exposing others . The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says that if you \u2019re sick or think you \u2019re sick , but only mildly ill , you should isolate yourself , and you should n\u2019t leave your house except to go to the doctor .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466746, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b50cc-7085-11ea-b456-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5100-7085-11ea-820f-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5134-7085-11ea-8c91-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I know when it \u2019s bad enough to get help ?", "answerText": "With so much advice telling people to stay home , it can be hard to know when emergency treatment is necessary . The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said these symptoms should prompt you to seek emergency care.\u2022 Difficulty breathing\u2022 Persistent pain or pressure in the chest\u2022 Confusion or inability to arouse\u2022 Bluish lips or face\u2022 Any other symptom that is severe or concerning Read MoreWhat to do if you or a loved one might have the coronavirus .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I know when it \u2019s bad enough to get help ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "With so much advice telling people to stay home , it can be hard to know when emergency treatment is necessary . The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said these symptoms should prompt you to seek emergency care.\u2022 Difficulty breathing\u2022 Persistent pain or pressure in the chest\u2022 Confusion or inability to arouse\u2022 Bluish lips or face\u2022 Any other symptom that is severe or concerning Read MoreWhat to do if you or a loved one might have the coronavirus .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466763, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5178-7085-11ea-896f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b51b4-7085-11ea-8f60-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b51e6-7085-11ea-91e3-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What if somebody in my family gets sick ?", "answerText": "If the family member does n\u2019t need hospitalization and can be cared for at home , you should help him or her with basic needs and monitor the symptoms , while also keeping as much distance as possible , according to guidelines issued by the C.D.C. in February . If there \u2019s space , the sick family member should stay in a separate room and use a separate bathroom to minimize contact with healthy family members . Any shared spaces should have good airflow , such as an open window or an air conditioner , and you should n\u2019t allow any visitors except for those who need to be in the house . Your family member should wear a face mask when he or she is around others , and if he or she ca n\u2019t because of difficulty breathing , you should wear a mask . Make sure not to share any dishes or other household items with your sick family member and to regularly clean surfaces like counters , doorknobs , toilets and tables . Do n\u2019t forget to wash your hands frequently .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What if somebody in my family gets sick ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "If the family member does n\u2019t need hospitalization and can be cared for at home , you should help him or her with basic needs and monitor the symptoms , while also keeping as much distance as possible , according to guidelines issued by the C.D.C. in February . If there \u2019s space , the sick family member should stay in a separate room and use a separate bathroom to minimize contact with healthy family members . Any shared spaces should have good airflow , such as an open window or an air conditioner , and you should n\u2019t allow any visitors except for those who need to be in the house . Your family member should wear a face mask when he or she is around others , and if he or she ca n\u2019t because of difficulty breathing , you should wear a mask . Make sure not to share any dishes or other household items with your sick family member and to regularly clean surfaces like counters , doorknobs , toilets and tables . Do n\u2019t forget to wash your hands frequently .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466781, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5236-7085-11ea-85ba-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5274-7085-11ea-92e2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b529a-7085-11ea-8f3d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why ca n\u2019t I just go to the doctor or the emergency room ?", "answerText": "\u201c If you show up unnecessarily , you \u2019re taking care away from people who really need it , \u201d writes Tara Parker - Pope , columnist for Well , The Times \u2019s consumer health section . \u201c Before going to the E.R. , stop and ask yourself , \u2018 Would I go to the E.R. for these symptoms ( a cough or fever ) under normal circumstances ? \u2019 In most cases , the answer is probably no . \u201d Instead , you should call ahead and ask a doctor or the emergency room for advice . They \u2019re likely to have the most up - to - date information for potential patients in your area , and they \u2019ll tell you what to do next . Read MoreWhat to do if you or a loved one might have the coronavirus .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why ca n\u2019t I just go to the doctor or the emergency room ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "\u201c If you show up unnecessarily , you \u2019re taking care away from people who really need it , \u201d writes Tara Parker - Pope , columnist for Well , The Times \u2019s consumer health section . \u201c Before going to the E.R. , stop and ask yourself , \u2018 Would I go to the E.R. for these symptoms ( a cough or fever ) under normal circumstances ? \u2019 In most cases , the answer is probably no . \u201d Instead , you should call ahead and ask a doctor or the emergency room for advice . They \u2019re likely to have the most up - to - date information for potential patients in your area , and they \u2019ll tell you what to do next . Read MoreWhat to do if you or a loved one might have the coronavirus .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4668002, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b52e8-7085-11ea-ba98-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b531c-7085-11ea-afcf-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5346-7085-11ea-805b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I get tested ?", "answerText": "If you \u2019re sick and you think you \u2019 ve been exposed to the new coronavirus , the C.D.C. recommends that you call your healthcare provider and explain your symptoms and fears . They will decide if you need to be tested .    But keep in mind that , across the country , sick people say they \u2019re not being tested . The obstacles range from a lack of testing kits to being rejected because you \u2019re asymptomatic . In other words : There \u2019s a chance you ca n\u2019t get tested , even if you think you need it .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I get tested ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "If you \u2019re sick and you think you \u2019ve been exposed to the new coronavirus , the C.D.C. recommends that you call your healthcare provider and explain your symptoms and fears . They will decide if you need to be tested .   But keep in mind that , across the country , sick people say they \u2019re not being tested . The obstacles range from a lack of testing kits to being rejected because you \u2019re asymptomatic . In other words : There \u2019s a chance you ca n\u2019t get tested , even if you think you need it .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466818, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b539e-7085-11ea-aa6c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b53d0-7085-11ea-80a4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5402-7085-11ea-a7f6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a vaccine yet ?", "answerText": "Not yet . But in mid - March , the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases announced    it was beginning the first testing in humans of an experimental vaccine . Such rapid development of a potential vaccine is unprecedented , and it was possible because researchers were able to use what they already knew about related coronaviruses that had caused other outbreaks , of SARS and MERS.Other companies , using different approaches , are also trying to manufacture coronavirus vaccines . But it \u2019s not certain they \u2019ll work yet . And despite the rapid progress , even if the vaccine is proved safe and effective against the virus , it will not be available for at least a year .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a vaccine yet ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Not yet . But in mid - March , the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases announced   it was beginning the first testing in humans of an experimental vaccine . Such rapid development of a potential vaccine is unprecedented , and it was possible because researchers were able to use what they already knew about related coronaviruses that had caused other outbreaks , of SARS and MERS.Other companies , using different approaches , are also trying to manufacture coronavirus vaccines . But it \u2019s not certain they \u2019ll work yet . And despite the rapid progress , even if the vaccine is proved safe and effective against the virus , it will not be available for at least a year .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466836, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5452-7085-11ea-91d6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5486-7085-11ea-bcfa-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b54ac-7085-11ea-b267-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I had the coronavirus , or probably did , and I feel fine now . Can I go about my life ?", "answerText": "The latest C.D.C. advice for people with Covid-19 who had symptoms is that they no longer need to self - isolate when:\u2022 they have had no fever for at least a full 72 hours without the use of medicine and\u2022 other symptoms have gotten better and\u2022 at least seven days have passed since their symptoms first started . But the guidance on this is changing all the time as we learn more .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I had the coronavirus , or probably did , and I feel fine now . Can I go about my life ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The latest C.D.C. advice for people with Covid-19 who had symptoms is that they no longer need to self - isolate when:\u2022 they have had no fever for at least a full 72 hours without the use of medicine and\u2022 other symptoms have gotten better and\u2022 at least seven days have passed since their symptoms first started . But the guidance on this is changing all the time as we learn more .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4668531, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b54fa-7085-11ea-a5e9-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b552e-7085-11ea-a7d2-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5558-7085-11ea-9eae-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Are people who get sick immune from the virus ?", "answerText": "The answer is a qualified yes , but there \u2019s a lot that is n\u2019t known yet . If people who survived Covid-19 were known to be immune to the virus , they could venture back outside , and into the workforce , until a vaccine became available for everyone else . In particular , health care workers who are known to be immune could continue to care for severely ill people . The quickest way to assess immunity to the coronavirus is a test that looks for protective antibodies in the blood of people who have recovered . But first you have to have the test . Labs around the world are working on such tests , but none are readily accessible quite yet . Read More                Here \u2019s what else researchers are trying to learn about immunity .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Are people who get sick immune from the virus ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The answer is a qualified yes , but there \u2019s a lot that is n\u2019t known yet . If people who survived Covid-19 were known to be immune to the virus , they could venture back outside , and into the workforce , until a vaccine became available for everyone else . In particular , health care workers who are known to be immune could continue to care for severely ill people . The quickest way to assess immunity to the coronavirus is a test that looks for protective antibodies in the blood of people who have recovered . But first you have to have the test . Labs around the world are working on such tests , but none are readily accessible quite yet . Read More               Here \u2019s what else researchers are trying to learn about immunity .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.46687, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b55a6-7085-11ea-ab90-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b55d8-7085-11ea-b81e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b560a-7085-11ea-b460-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I wear a mask ?", "answerText": "Experts are divided on how much protection a regular surgical mask , or even a scarf , can provide for people who are n\u2019t yet sick . The W.H.O. and C.D.C. say that unless you \u2019re already sick , or caring for someone who is , wearing a face mask while you go about your daily life is n\u2019t necessary . Masks do n\u2019t replace hand - washing and social distancing . And stockpiling high - grade N95 masks can do more harm than good , making it harder for nurses and other workers to access the resources they need to help on the front lines . But researchers are also finding that there are more cases of asymptomatic transmission than were known early on in the pandemic , especially through younger people who have mild cases and do n\u2019t know they are sick but are still infectious . And a few experts say that masks could offer some protection in crowded places , like subways , buses or other public gatherings where it is not possible to stay 6 feet away from other people .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I wear a mask ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Experts are divided on how much protection a regular surgical mask , or even a scarf , can provide for people who are n\u2019t yet sick . The W.H.O. and C.D.C. say that unless you \u2019re already sick , or caring for someone who is , wearing a face mask while you go about your daily life is n\u2019t necessary . Masks do n\u2019t replace hand - washing and social distancing . And stockpiling high - grade N95 masks can do more harm than good , making it harder for nurses and other workers to access the resources they need to help on the front lines . But researchers are also finding that there are more cases of asymptomatic transmission than were known early on in the pandemic , especially through younger people who have mild cases and do n\u2019t know they are sick but are still infectious . And a few experts say that masks could offer some protection in crowded places , like subways , buses or other public gatherings where it is not possible to stay 6 feet away from other people .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4668858, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5646-7085-11ea-af82-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b566e-7085-11ea-ba07-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b569e-7085-11ea-a848-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is it different from the flu ?", "answerText": "The flu and the coronavirus can cause similar symptoms \u2014 a whole - body malaise , with a fever , a dry cough and a noticeable shortness of breath \u2014 but there are differences . Because the symptoms are so similar , doctors will sometimes rule out the flu first . Spring allergy season tends to trigger many of the same symptoms in many people , adding another diagnostic wrinkle . Read More                Here \u2019s how to tell the difference .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is it different from the flu ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The flu and the coronavirus can cause similar symptoms \u2014 a whole - body malaise , with a fever , a dry cough and a noticeable shortness of breath \u2014 but there are differences . Because the symptoms are so similar , doctors will sometimes rule out the flu first . Spring allergy season tends to trigger many of the same symptoms in many people , adding another diagnostic wrinkle . Read More               Here \u2019s how to tell the difference .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466902, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b56e6-7085-11ea-b4ca-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5718-7085-11ea-bf4a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5740-7085-11ea-b35f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a natural cure for the coronavirus ?", "answerText": "There is no proven cure for the coronavirus . But that has not stopped people ( and some businesses ) from claiming to have found one . Despite what you may have read online : Gargling with warm water will not keep you from getting the coronavirus . Neither will elderberry syrup or colloidal silver . Essential oils are not a good substitute for hand sanitizer . The authorities are cracking down on those seeking to capitalize on peoples \u2019 fears and anxieties right now . The F.D.A. sent warning letters to at least seven companies telling them to stop advertising fraudulent cures and treatments . The New York State attorney general ordered Alex Jones , the conservative radio host , to stop claiming that his diet supplements and toothpaste could be used to fight the coronavirus . Read MoreThat \u2018 miracle cure \u2019 you saw on Facebook wo n\u2019t make you healthy .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a natural cure for the coronavirus ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "There is no proven cure for the coronavirus . But that has not stopped people ( and some businesses ) from claiming to have found one . Despite what you may have read online : Gargling with warm water will not keep you from getting the coronavirus . Neither will elderberry syrup or colloidal silver . Essential oils are not a good substitute for hand sanitizer . The authorities are cracking down on those seeking to capitalize on peoples \u2019 fears and anxieties right now . The F.D.A. sent warning letters to at least seven companies telling them to stop advertising fraudulent cures and treatments . The New York State attorney general ordered Alex Jones , the conservative radio host , to stop claiming that his diet supplements and toothpaste could be used to fight the coronavirus . Read MoreThat \u2018 miracle cure \u2019 you saw on Facebook wo n\u2019t make you healthy .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466917, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5786-7085-11ea-bcf6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b57ae-7085-11ea-baa7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b57e2-7085-11ea-b55f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I give blood ?", "answerText": "You can . Donor blood is not being used to treat coronavirus patients , but transfusions are still needed for cases like organ transplants or complications of childbirth . But thousands of community blood drives have been canceled , cutting short a crucial supply . The American Red Cross is still collecting donations at blood banks , which have enacted new safety measures to prevent the spread of the coronavirus . Those measures include checking the temperatures of staff members and donors before they enter a drive facility , providing hand sanitizer for use before and during the donation process , enhancing their disinfection of surfaces and equipment , and spacing beds \u2014 when possible \u2014 to enable social distancing between donors . And even if you \u2019re under a stay - at - home order , donating blood is an essential need , so public health officials have made an exception for your trip to the donation center . To find a donation center , check the American Association of Blood Banks locator , visit the Red Cross website or call 1 - 800-RED - CROSS . Read More                Here \u2019s how to donate blood during the outbreak .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I give blood ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "You can . Donor blood is not being used to treat coronavirus patients , but transfusions are still needed for cases like organ transplants or complications of childbirth . But thousands of community blood drives have been canceled , cutting short a crucial supply . The American Red Cross is still collecting donations at blood banks , which have enacted new safety measures to prevent the spread of the coronavirus . Those measures include checking the temperatures of staff members and donors before they enter a drive facility , providing hand sanitizer for use before and during the donation process , enhancing their disinfection of surfaces and equipment , and spacing beds \u2014 when possible \u2014 to enable social distancing between donors . And even if you \u2019re under a stay - at - home order , donating blood is an essential need , so public health officials have made an exception for your trip to the donation center . To find a donation center , check the American Association of Blood Banks locator , visit the Red Cross website or call 1 - 800-RED - CROSS . Read More               Here \u2019s how to donate blood during the outbreak .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466936, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5830-7085-11ea-8ef7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5862-7085-11ea-8654-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5894-7085-11ea-8264-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Where can I donate ?", "answerText": "Charity Navigator , which evaluates charities using a numbers - based system , has a running list of nonprofits working in communities affected by the outbreak . More than 20,000 coronavirus - related GoFundMe fund - raisers have started in the past few weeks . ( The sheer number of fund - raisers means more of them are likely to fail to meet their goal , though . ) Read MoreYou can find more relief organizations and ways to give here .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Where can I donate ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Charity Navigator , which evaluates charities using a numbers - based system , has a running list of nonprofits working in communities affected by the outbreak . More than 20,000 coronavirus - related GoFundMe fund - raisers have started in the past few weeks . ( The sheer number of fund - raisers means more of them are likely to fail to meet their goal , though . ) Read MoreYou can find more relief organizations and ways to give here .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.46695, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b58c6-7085-11ea-9d93-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b58f8-7085-11ea-98d9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b591e-7085-11ea-8c15-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Want to give toward medical supplies ?", "answerText": "Relief International , which operates in 16 countries throughout Africa , the Middle East and Asia , has focused some of its efforts on helping Iran , where more than 20,000 infections and at least 1,500 deaths have been reported . Heart to Heart International is distributing urgently needed equipment and medication to its partners around the world . Medical supplies are also being delivered to providers on the front lines .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Want to give toward medical supplies ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Relief International , which operates in 16 countries throughout Africa , the Middle East and Asia , has focused some of its efforts on helping Iran , where more than 20,000 infections and at least 1,500 deaths have been reported . Heart to Heart International is distributing urgently needed equipment and medication to its partners around the world . Medical supplies are also being delivered to providers on the front lines .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466967, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5966-7085-11ea-a4b8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5998-7085-11ea-a813-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b59ca-7085-11ea-880f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Want to simply give money ?", "answerText": "GlobalGiving is a large global crowdfunding community that connects nonprofits , donors and companies . It has set a goal of reaching $ 5 million in donations . Money received will go toward sending emergency medical workers to communities in need , providing medical supplies to hospitals and helping deliver essentials to families .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Want to simply give money ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "GlobalGiving is a large global crowdfunding community that connects nonprofits , donors and companies . It has set a goal of reaching $ 5 million in donations . Money received will go toward sending emergency medical workers to communities in need , providing medical supplies to hospitals and helping deliver essentials to families .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4669828, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5a10-7085-11ea-803a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5a42-7085-11ea-a803-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5a68-7085-11ea-ac9b-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have a sewing machine . Can I make masks ?", "answerText": "You can ! There are patterns circulating online , and some sewing stores have been handing out kits . They wo n\u2019t be the high - grade N95 masks that are the most effective devices to filter out the coronavirus , nor will they even be as tough as surgical masks . But the D.I.Y. pieces offer at least some protection . Some doctors are wearing the homemade fabrics over surgical or N95 masks , trying to prolong the coveted masks \u2019 limited life spans . Other masks are being handed out at health clinics and nursing homes . \u201c It frees up the surgical masks for the people who are the highest risk , \u201d Dr. Nicole Seminara , a doctor at NYU Langone Health , told The Times .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have a sewing machine . Can I make masks ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "You can ! There are patterns circulating online , and some sewing stores have been handing out kits . They wo n\u2019t be the high - grade N95 masks that are the most effective devices to filter out the coronavirus , nor will they even be as tough as surgical masks . But the D.I.Y. pieces offer at least some protection . Some doctors are wearing the homemade fabrics over surgical or N95 masks , trying to prolong the coveted masks \u2019 limited life spans . Other masks are being handed out at health clinics and nursing homes . \u201cIt frees up the surgical masks for the people who are the highest risk , \u201d Dr. Nicole Seminara , a doctor at NYU Langone Health , told The Times .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.466999, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5ab0-7085-11ea-a8bc-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5ae2-7085-11ea-ab4e-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5b14-7085-11ea-ae8e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I \u2019 m worried about my favorite local business .", "answerText": "By the time the coronavirus crisis is over , we might emerge from our homes only to find some of our favorite shops , restaurants and other local businesses permanently shuttered . As part of the sweeping stimulus bill , federally guaranteed loans would be available at community banks to small businesses that pledge not to lay off their workers . One way you as an individual could help your favorite small business would be to consider buying a gift card online .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I \u2019m worried about my favorite local business .", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "By the time the coronavirus crisis is over , we might emerge from our homes only to find some of our favorite shops , restaurants and other local businesses permanently shuttered . As part of the sweeping stimulus bill , federally guaranteed loans would be available at community banks to small businesses that pledge not to lay off their workers . One way you as an individual could help your favorite small business would be to consider buying a gift card online .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467015, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5b5a-7085-11ea-9075-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5b8c-7085-11ea-8ec8-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5bbe-7085-11ea-969a-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I have older neighbors . How can I help them ?", "answerText": "Older people seem to be particularly susceptible to contracting the coronavirus , according to health officials . Some are staying at home and , as a precaution , may not open their doors to visitors . One way to check on homebound older residents without jeopardizing their health is to call or send a text , said Eric . S. Goldstein , the chief executive officer of the UJA - Federation of New York , which provides food , health care and other services to people in need . If telephone calls and texts are not an option , \u201c talk through the door , \u201d Mr. Goldstein said . Because some people may recoil at the suggestion that they are not self - sufficient , Mr. Goldstein suggested offering to help in a low - key way , such as saying , \u201c I \u2019 m running to the market , can I get you anything ? \u201d", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I have older neighbors . How can I help them ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Older people seem to be particularly susceptible to contracting the coronavirus , according to health officials . Some are staying at home and , as a precaution , may not open their doors to visitors . One way to check on homebound older residents without jeopardizing their health is to call or send a text , said Eric . S. Goldstein , the chief executive officer of the UJA - Federation of New York , which provides food , health care and other services to people in need . If telephone calls and texts are not an option , \u201c talk through the door , \u201d Mr. Goldstein said . Because some people may recoil at the suggestion that they are not self - sufficient , Mr. Goldstein suggested offering to help in a low - key way , such as saying , \u201c I \u2019m running to the market , can I get you anything ? \u201d", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467034, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5c0c-7085-11ea-a756-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5c40-7085-11ea-8fb9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5c68-7085-11ea-99cc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What does \u2018 stay at home \u2019 mean ?", "answerText": "Authorities in different states have used different phrases while asking people to stay home . Generally , it means you should limit trips outside except for essential needs . You can still go for walks and exercise , but do it in a way that keeps you several feet away from other people . You can still go to the grocery store , but try to go once a week instead of more frequently . And wash your hands when you come back inside .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What does \u2018 stay at home \u2019 mean ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Authorities in different states have used different phrases while asking people to stay home . Generally , it means you should limit trips outside except for essential needs . You can still go for walks and exercise , but do it in a way that keeps you several feet away from other people . You can still go to the grocery store , but try to go once a week instead of more frequently . And wash your hands when you come back inside .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467051, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5cc2-7085-11ea-b952-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5cf4-7085-11ea-be8a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5d1c-7085-11ea-8a50-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I \u2019 m stuck inside . Help ?", "answerText": "Stay home to flatten the curve , and do n\u2019t lose your mind by doing different activities like working your way through the best 50 movies on Netflix right now , or by checking out the books on the nightstand you \u2019 ve been ignoring . Looking for new reading material ? Check out this list of 52 books for 52 places so you can escape to a far away destination without dealing with travel restrictions or risk of illness . Be sure to get up and stretch , because exercise can help burn off pent up energy . Here \u2019s a quick guide to an at - home workout where the only equipment you need is a resistance band . While you \u2019re moving , spend some time disinfecting surfaces in your home to keep everything clean . The C.D.C. recommends you clean and disinfect high - contact surfaces , including tables , doorknobs , light switches , countertops , handles , desks , phones , keyboards , toilets , faucets and sinks every day .    And check in with your loved ones . Social distancing does n\u2019t mean disconnecting from those you care about , and older relatives and friends are susceptible to loneliness , which researchers have found comes with its own set of health hazards . So make sure to FaceTime your parents and grandparents . And if you have done all of those things , watch this video of Arnold Schwarzenegger feeding a pony and a donkey in his kitchen .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I \u2019m stuck inside . Help ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Stay home to flatten the curve , and do n\u2019t lose your mind by doing different activities like working your way through the best 50 movies on Netflix right now , or by checking out the books on the nightstand you \u2019ve been ignoring . Looking for new reading material ? Check out this list of 52 books for 52 places so you can escape to a far away destination without dealing with travel restrictions or risk of illness . Be sure to get up and stretch , because exercise can help burn off pent up energy . Here \u2019s a quick guide to an at - home workout where the only equipment you need is a resistance band . While you \u2019re moving , spend some time disinfecting surfaces in your home to keep everything clean . The C.D.C. recommends you clean and disinfect high - contact surfaces , including tables , doorknobs , light switches , countertops , handles , desks , phones , keyboards , toilets , faucets and sinks every day .   And check in with your loved ones . Social distancing does n\u2019t mean disconnecting from those you care about , and older relatives and friends are susceptible to loneliness , which researchers have found comes with its own set of health hazards . So make sure to FaceTime your parents and grandparents . And if you have done all of those things , watch this video of Arnold Schwarzenegger feeding a pony and a donkey in his kitchen .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467069, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5d76-7085-11ea-8e77-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5da8-7085-11ea-a4eb-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5dd0-7085-11ea-848c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is it ethical to order delivery in a pandemic ?", "answerText": "It \u2019s a complicated question , right ? Officials are telling us to stay indoors and away from others . At the same time , you need food or , as importantly , medicine . But what about the health of the delivery workers who come to your door ? How do we keep each other safe?For older Americans and those with health problems who are most at risk if they contract the coronavirus , having goods delivered makes sense . Some companies , like Postmates and Instacart , have begun offering non - contact or curbside deliveries . European companies are doing it , too . Those services have a large network in place , though , which means their businesses are likely to thrive . Smaller retailers will not as Americans eschew restaurants , bars and specialty stores . That is why some restaurants are promoting delivery services as a way to stay in business , and why some cities that have ordered restaurants and bars to close have made exceptions for places providing delivery and takeout . But what about delivery workers ? Some groups , like Gig Workers Rising , are demanding that employers like Doordash and Instacart do more to protect them on the job . Recently , the group started a petition asking companies to provide paid time off to drivers who become sick during the coronavirus outbreak and can not work . The bottom line is this : Online deliveries are a boon for those who can not leave their homes , as well as small restaurants who fear going out of business . But at the same time it comes with a risk to drivers and delivery workers who fear the loss of income if they get sick . At a minimum , everyone should generously tip their drivers for the service . Read MoreRead an essay in our Opinion section by a food - delivery driver .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is it ethical to order delivery in a pandemic ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "It \u2019s a complicated question , right ? Officials are telling us to stay indoors and away from others . At the same time , you need food or , as importantly , medicine . But what about the health of the delivery workers who come to your door ? How do we keep each other safe?For older Americans and those with health problems who are most at risk if they contract the coronavirus , having goods delivered makes sense . Some companies , like Postmates and Instacart , have begun offering non - contact or curbside deliveries . European companies are doing it , too . Those services have a large network in place , though , which means their businesses are likely to thrive . Smaller retailers will not as Americans eschew restaurants , bars and specialty stores . That is why some restaurants are promoting delivery services as a way to stay in business , and why some cities that have ordered restaurants and bars to close have made exceptions for places providing delivery and takeout . But what about delivery workers ? Some groups , like Gig Workers Rising , are demanding that employers like Doordash and Instacart do more to protect them on the job . Recently , the group started a petition asking companies to provide paid time off to drivers who become sick during the coronavirus outbreak and can not work . The bottom line is this : Online deliveries are a boon for those who can not leave their homes , as well as small restaurants who fear going out of business . But at the same time it comes with a risk to drivers and delivery workers who fear the loss of income if they get sick . At a minimum , everyone should generously tip their drivers for the service . Read MoreRead an essay in our Opinion section by a food - delivery driver .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467086, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5e18-7085-11ea-a0bd-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5e48-7085-11ea-ae65-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5e70-7085-11ea-815c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How do I make working at home easier ?", "answerText": "It \u2019s a tough one . The writer Jen A. Miller offers these tips : Keep the same schedule , schedule breaks and proactively stay in touch with others to avoid suffering from isolation . That could mean emailing colleagues more often or holding video conferences to keep in touch . If all else fails , get a dog . At the end of the day , put away your laptop and other work materials so that you can unwind . Read More                Are you wondering about whether the internet can handle so many us working from home ? Here you go .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How do I make working at home easier ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "It \u2019s a tough one . The writer Jen A. Miller offers these tips : Keep the same schedule , schedule breaks and proactively stay in touch with others to avoid suffering from isolation . That could mean emailing colleagues more often or holding video conferences to keep in touch . If all else fails , get a dog . At the end of the day , put away your laptop and other work materials so that you can unwind . Read More               Are you wondering about whether the internet can handle so many us working from home ? Here you go .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467104, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5ed4-7085-11ea-a738-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5efa-7085-11ea-b335-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5f2e-7085-11ea-860d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I stock up on groceries ?", "answerText": "No one knows how long many of us will have to work from or stay home , so having food and supplies on hand is essential . Melissa Clark , a cookbook author and food writer for the Times , recently wrote about stocking your pantry .        But experts say people should not hoard food or supplies . Despite the empty appearance of store shelves , food suppliers and retailers say the supply chain remains strong . In the meantime , plan two weeks of meals . Substitute ingredients if you are missing something . Be creative . And do n\u2019t forget to be generous with your neighbors .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I stock up on groceries ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "No one knows how long many of us will have to work from or stay home , so having food and supplies on hand is essential . Melissa Clark , a cookbook author and food writer for the Times , recently wrote about stocking your pantry .       But experts say people should not hoard food or supplies . Despite the empty appearance of store shelves , food suppliers and retailers say the supply chain remains strong . In the meantime , plan two weeks of meals . Substitute ingredients if you are missing something . Be creative . And do n\u2019t forget to be generous with your neighbors .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4671202, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b5f68-7085-11ea-854b-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b5f92-7085-11ea-9341-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b5fc6-7085-11ea-919e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I have friends over ?", "answerText": "You should n\u2019t . As the outbreak has progressed , officials around the world have banned increasingly smaller gatherings : 500 people , to 250 , to 50 , to 10 . In mid - March , Germany banned groups larger than two . Social distancing means that unless you are already sharing a home with someone , you should not interact with them if you can help it . Instead of having people over for dinner or a game night , try talking to them outside \u2014 while you all stay several feet apart .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I have friends over ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "You should n\u2019t . As the outbreak has progressed , officials around the world have banned increasingly smaller gatherings : 500 people , to 250 , to 50 , to 10 . In mid - March , Germany banned groups larger than two . Social distancing means that unless you are already sharing a home with someone , you should not interact with them if you can help it . Instead of having people over for dinner or a game night , try talking to them outside \u2014 while you all stay several feet apart .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467135, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6000-7085-11ea-b67f-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b603a-7085-11ea-b4a7-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6064-7085-11ea-9b60-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I still get mail ?", "answerText": "The U.S. Postal Service , UPS and FedEx are still delivering the mail , but to continue doing so requires a healthy work force , and at least 20 postal workers have tested positive for the virus . Workers for UPS and FedEx share similar fears about contracting the virus , especially at warehouses where the mail is handled . Increasingly , letter carriers and delivery people are leaving packages on doorsteps and limiting close interaction with residents . A recent study found that the virus disintegrates over about 24 hours on cardboard , suggesting that packages may have only low levels of the virus \u2014 unless the delivery person has coughed or sneezed on it or has handled it with contaminated hands . If you are concerned about the risk , wipe down packages with disinfectant wipes and wash your hands . Read MorePostal workers are worried about getting sick .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I still get mail ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The U.S. Postal Service , UPS and FedEx are still delivering the mail , but to continue doing so requires a healthy work force , and at least 20 postal workers have tested positive for the virus . Workers for UPS and FedEx share similar fears about contracting the virus , especially at warehouses where the mail is handled . Increasingly , letter carriers and delivery people are leaving packages on doorsteps and limiting close interaction with residents . A recent study found that the virus disintegrates over about 24 hours on cardboard , suggesting that packages may have only low levels of the virus \u2014 unless the delivery person has coughed or sneezed on it or has handled it with contaminated hands . If you are concerned about the risk , wipe down packages with disinfectant wipes and wash your hands . Read MorePostal workers are worried about getting sick .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4671512, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b609e-7085-11ea-b540-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b60d2-7085-11ea-bf5d-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b60fa-7085-11ea-9c7f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How can I exercise if I \u2019 m cooped up all day ?", "answerText": "Gyms are closed , and you ca n\u2019t get close to people , so contact sports are out of the question . But it \u2019s still possible to get your heart pumping and body moving . A running boom is taking off , courtesy of the coronavirus , and several gyms , health clubs and yoga studios are now offering classes online . \u201c Every little bit of movement counts , \u201d said Dani Johnson , a physical therapist at the Mayo Clinic Healthy Living Program . \u201c So when we \u2019re confined to our home , move , move , move . \u201d You do n\u2019t need fancy equipment or a lot of time ; you just need to weave exercise into your schedule . Read More                If you \u2019re going to take up running , here \u2019s how to do it safely .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How can I exercise if I \u2019m cooped up all day ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Gyms are closed , and you ca n\u2019t get close to people , so contact sports are out of the question . But it \u2019s still possible to get your heart pumping and body moving . A running boom is taking off , courtesy of the coronavirus , and several gyms , health clubs and yoga studios are now offering classes online . \u201c Every little bit of movement counts , \u201d said Dani Johnson , a physical therapist at the Mayo Clinic Healthy Living Program . \u201c So when we \u2019re confined to our home , move , move , move . \u201dYou do n\u2019t need fancy equipment or a lot of time ; you just need to weave exercise into your schedule . Read More               If you \u2019re going to take up running , here \u2019s how to do it safely .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467169, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6154-7085-11ea-a25e-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b617a-7085-11ea-99f4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b61ae-7085-11ea-b684-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I get my pet sick ? Can my pet get me sick ?", "answerText": "There is no evidence that pets such as dogs or cats can spread the coronavirus , according to the World Health Organization and the C.D.C. A dog owned by a coronavirus patient in Hong Kong showed some level of virus in its nose and mouth , what researchers called a \u201c weak positive . \u201d But health authorities said it was likely a case of a human transmitting it to the dog , not the other way around , and that people should not be worried about the welfare of their pets .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I get my pet sick ? Can my pet get me sick ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "There is no evidence that pets such as dogs or cats can spread the coronavirus , according to the World Health Organization and the C.D.C. A dog owned by a coronavirus patient in Hong Kong showed some level of virus in its nose and mouth , what researchers called a \u201c weak positive . \u201d But health authorities said it was likely a case of a human transmitting it to the dog , not the other way around , and that people should not be worried about the welfare of their pets .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467184, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b61e8-7085-11ea-a31c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6226-7085-11ea-94b9-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6258-7085-11ea-9659-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My kids are scared . What can I tell them ?", "answerText": "Before you talk to your children , it \u2019s important to understand your own anxiety and keep it in check . If your child is worried about the coronavirus , listen to him or her , rather than respond with comments like , \u201c It \u2019ll be fine . \u201d Dismissive reactions can make children feel like they \u2019re not being heard , said Abi Gewirtz , a clinical psychologist and professor at the University of Minnesota . Emphasize the importance of washing hands after using the bathroom and before or after meals . Children ( and adults ) should sing \u201c Happy Birthday \u201d twice to make sure they \u2019 ve been washing their hands for at least 20 seconds . You should also frame school cancellation as positive \u2014 more time to have more fun at home ! \u2014    and encourage your children to get exercise .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My kids are scared . What can I tell them ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Before you talk to your children , it \u2019s important to understand your own anxiety and keep it in check . If your child is worried about the coronavirus , listen to him or her , rather than respond with comments like , \u201c It \u2019ll be fine . \u201d Dismissive reactions can make children feel like they \u2019re not being heard , said Abi Gewirtz , a clinical psychologist and professor at the University of Minnesota . Emphasize the importance of washing hands after using the bathroom and before or after meals . Children ( and adults ) should sing \u201c Happy Birthday \u201d twice to make sure they \u2019ve been washing their hands for at least 20 seconds . You should also frame school cancellation as positive \u2014 more time to have more fun at home ! \u2014   and encourage your children to get exercise .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467202, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b629e-7085-11ea-ad2a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b62d0-7085-11ea-b1fc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b62f8-7085-11ea-94fc-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My state is n\u2019t under any orders to stay at home . So I do n\u2019t have to , right ?", "answerText": "The situation is changing daily , as it becomes clear the outbreak has spread to more parts of the country . The federal government is largely leaving the decision up to states , and some state leaders are leaving the decision up to local authorities . Even if you are n\u2019t being told to stay at home , it \u2019s still a good idea to limit trips outside and your interaction with other people .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My state is n\u2019t under any orders to stay at home . So I do n\u2019t have to , right ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The situation is changing daily , as it becomes clear the outbreak has spread to more parts of the country . The federal government is largely leaving the decision up to states , and some state leaders are leaving the decision up to local authorities . Even if you are n\u2019t being told to stay at home , it \u2019s still a good idea to limit trips outside and your interaction with other people .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467217, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6334-7085-11ea-beaf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6366-7085-11ea-be81-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b638c-7085-11ea-881d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I go to the park ?", "answerText": "Yes ! Getting exercise outside is a great alternative to going to the gym , where touching high - contact equipment can pose a risk ( if your gym is even still open ) . A study last year found infectious germs on about a third of the surfaces at 16 different fitness facilities . Exercise boosts our immune systems , and even a single workout can improve our ability to fight off germs , according to the latest research . Even if you just hang out in a park , rather than go for a jog or a walk , getting some fresh air , and hopefully sunshine , is a good idea .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I go to the park ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Yes ! Getting exercise outside is a great alternative to going to the gym , where touching high - contact equipment can pose a risk ( if your gym is even still open ) . A study last year found infectious germs on about a third of the surfaces at 16 different fitness facilities . Exercise boosts our immune systems , and even a single workout can improve our ability to fight off germs , according to the latest research . Even if you just hang out in a park , rather than go for a jog or a walk , getting some fresh air , and hopefully sunshine , is a good idea .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4672341, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b63de-7085-11ea-90e7-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6410-7085-11ea-bbfc-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6438-7085-11ea-b790-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Should I get on the subway ? Go to the grocery store ?", "answerText": "This decision is personal and depends on your tolerance for risk . Many places around the world have ordered \u2014 or strongly urged \u2014 residents to stay indoors , unless they absolutely need to be outside . If you can avoid the subway , that may be smart , but if you ca n\u2019t , there are things you can do to minimize your risk . Avoid jam - packed cars . If you need to hold onto a pole , use a disposable glove that you can throw away when you leave the subway . Avoid touching your face . At the grocery store , wipe the handle of the grocery cart with a disinfecting wipe and wash your hands as soon as you get home .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Should I get on the subway ? Go to the grocery store ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "This decision is personal and depends on your tolerance for risk . Many places around the world have ordered \u2014 or strongly urged \u2014 residents to stay indoors , unless they absolutely need to be outside . If you can avoid the subway , that may be smart , but if you ca n\u2019t , there are things you can do to minimize your risk . Avoid jam - packed cars . If you need to hold onto a pole , use a disposable glove that you can throw away when you leave the subway . Avoid touching your face . At the grocery store , wipe the handle of the grocery cart with a disinfecting wipe and wash your hands as soon as you get home .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4672499, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6488-7085-11ea-a382-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b64b0-7085-11ea-871b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b64e2-7085-11ea-911c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What \u2019s an essential service ? Who decides that ?", "answerText": "In places where officials have called for workplaces to be shuttered , there are exemptions for \u201c essential \u201d services and businesses . Those institutions can remain open for customers and have workers onsite . In the United States there are federal guidelines for what is considered an essential service , but decisions are often made at the state level . For example , here are some lists of essential services in New York , Massachusetts , California and Illinois . All four states consider pharmacies , gas stations , laundromats and groceries to be essential , and all of them say restaurants can stay open for take - out and delivery orders . Typically , essential services also include utilities , telecommunications and transportation providers ; animal shelters and veterinary services ; manufacturers and distributors of basic goods ; and child care for those who work in essential services .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What \u2019s an essential service ? Who decides that ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "In places where officials have called for workplaces to be shuttered , there are exemptions for \u201c essential \u201d services and businesses . Those institutions can remain open for customers and have workers onsite . In the United States there are federal guidelines for what is considered an essential service , but decisions are often made at the state level . For example , here are some lists of essential services in New York , Massachusetts , California and Illinois . All four states consider pharmacies , gas stations , laundromats and groceries to be essential , and all of them say restaurants can stay open for take - out and delivery orders . Typically , essential services also include utilities , telecommunications and transportation providers ; animal shelters and veterinary services ; manufacturers and distributors of basic goods ; and child care for those who work in essential services .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467266, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b651e-7085-11ea-8dc6-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6550-7085-11ea-aa01-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6578-7085-11ea-805c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I take my laundry to a laundromat ? Is that safe ?", "answerText": "The C.D.C. has guidelines about laundry . It says do not shake dirty laundry , to minimize the possibility of dispersing the virus through the air . If possible , wash items using the warmest water setting , and dry thoroughly . Dirty laundry that has been in contact with an ill person can be washed with other people \u2019s items , the C.D.C. said . Clean and disinfect hampers or other carts for transporting laundry , according to the guidelines for cleaning surfaces . The need for physical distancing has prompted some laundromats to dismantle their seating areas , according to Planet Laundry , the magazine of the Coin Laundry Association . Some laundromats are asking people to stay in their cars during their wash and dry cycles , and some have removed chairs and tables to discourage people from mingling . Commercial - grade washers and dryers operate at higher temperatures and with more rigorous mechanical action that , when combined with hot water and proper detergent use , can effectively flush contaminants from clothing better than residential machines , says the association , which represents 30,000 small businesses .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I take my laundry to a laundromat ? Is that safe ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The C.D.C. has guidelines about laundry . It says do not shake dirty laundry , to minimize the possibility of dispersing the virus through the air . If possible , wash items using the warmest water setting , and dry thoroughly . Dirty laundry that has been in contact with an ill person can be washed with other people \u2019s items , the C.D.C. said . Clean and disinfect hampers or other carts for transporting laundry , according to the guidelines for cleaning surfaces . The need for physical distancing has prompted some laundromats to dismantle their seating areas , according to Planet Laundry , the magazine of the Coin Laundry Association . Some laundromats are asking people to stay in their cars during their wash and dry cycles , and some have removed chairs and tables to discourage people from mingling . Commercial - grade washers and dryers operate at higher temperatures and with more rigorous mechanical action that , when combined with hot water and proper detergent use , can effectively flush contaminants from clothing better than residential machines , says the association , which represents 30,000 small businesses .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467284, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b65d2-7085-11ea-8d7d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b660c-7085-11ea-bf80-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6640-7085-11ea-91e6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I visit my grandparents ?", "answerText": "You should n\u2019t . But if Skype , FaceTime or another app is an option , you can make a virtual visit . And there \u2019s always the old - fashioned telephone call , too . The virus is especially bad for older people like your grandma and grandpa , which means it \u2019s even more important for them to stay away from other people . It can be hard , but this keeps them healthier .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I visit my grandparents ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "You should n\u2019t . But if Skype , FaceTime or another app is an option , you can make a virtual visit . And there \u2019s always the old - fashioned telephone call , too . The virus is especially bad for older people like your grandma and grandpa , which means it \u2019s even more important for them to stay away from other people . It can be hard , but this keeps them healthier .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4673018, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6686-7085-11ea-89ae-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b66ae-7085-11ea-b546-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b66e2-7085-11ea-b05d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I play on the playground ?", "answerText": "Probably not . You should n't touch the slides or swings ( the virus can live on them , whether they are plastic or metal ) , and you 'd have to stay about six feet away from other kids . Maybe go to a field and try a game of catch with one of your parents .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I play on the playground ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Probably not . You should n't touch the slides or swings ( the virus can live on them , whether they are plastic or metal ) , and you 'd have to stay about six feet away from other kids . Maybe go to a field and try a game of catch with one of your parents .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467318, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6726-7085-11ea-83c4-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6758-7085-11ea-be67-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6780-7085-11ea-a042-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My school is closed . When will it reopen ?", "answerText": "It depends . Schools are closed for different lengths of time , and it 's unclear when it will be safe to go back . Some schools are trying learning - from - home programs , and others are offering free lunches for pick - up . Ask your parents .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My school is closed . When will it reopen ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "It depends . Schools are closed for different lengths of time , and it 's unclear when it will be safe to go back . Some schools are trying learning - from - home programs , and others are offering free lunches for pick - up . Ask your parents .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4673338, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b67c6-7085-11ea-87cf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b67f8-7085-11ea-a955-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b681e-7085-11ea-ab93-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I have a playdate ?", "answerText": "Probably not . You 'd have to stay about six feet away from your friend . Maybe a bike ride or walk , with some distance between you ? Or you could try a video - chat if that 's an option .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I have a playdate ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Probably not . You 'd have to stay about six feet away from your friend . Maybe a bike ride or walk , with some distance between you ? Or you could try a video - chat if that 's an option .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467349, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b685c-7085-11ea-bb56-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6886-7085-11ea-96bd-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b68b6-7085-11ea-982f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why is it called the coronavirus ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses that infect animals and people . In February , the W.H.O. gave official names to both this virus ( SARS - CoV-2 , for severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 ) and the disease it causes ( Covid-19 , for coronavirus disease 2019 ) . You may have heard it called the \u201c new \u201d or \u201c novel \u201d coronavirus , and those mean just what they sound like : that it \u2019s new .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why is it called the coronavirus ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses that infect animals and people . In February , the W.H.O. gave official names to both this virus ( SARS - CoV-2 , for severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 ) and the disease it causes ( Covid-19 , for coronavirus disease 2019 ) . You may have heard it called the \u201c new \u201d or \u201c novel \u201d coronavirus , and those mean just what they sound like : that it \u2019s new .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467364, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b68e8-7085-11ea-918c-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b691a-7085-11ea-93f5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6942-7085-11ea-8f35-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How does it spread ?", "answerText": "It seems to spread very easily from person to person , especially in homes , hospitals and other confined spaces . The pathogen can be carried on tiny respiratory droplets that fall as they are coughed or sneezed out . Read More                Here \u2019s more about the latest research .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How does it spread ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "It seems to spread very easily from person to person , especially in homes , hospitals and other confined spaces . The pathogen can be carried on tiny respiratory droplets that fall as they are coughed or sneezed out . Read More               Here \u2019s more about the latest research .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467378, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b697e-7085-11ea-a665-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b69b0-7085-11ea-8ab6-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b69d8-7085-11ea-ada0-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What makes this outbreak so different ?", "answerText": "Unlike the flu , there is no known treatment or vaccine , and little is known about this particular virus so far . It seems to be more lethal than the flu , but the numbers are still uncertain . And it hits the elderly and those with underlying conditions particularly hard \u2014 not just those with respiratory diseases .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What makes this outbreak so different ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Unlike the flu , there is no known treatment or vaccine , and little is known about this particular virus so far . It seems to be more lethal than the flu , but the numbers are still uncertain . And it hits the elderly and those with underlying conditions particularly hard \u2014 not just those with respiratory diseases .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467395, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6a34-7085-11ea-b680-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6a5a-7085-11ea-8e91-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6a8c-7085-11ea-a8a9-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I heard ibuprofen does n\u2019t work . Is that true ?", "answerText": "The health minister of France , Olivier V\u00e9ran , recently left global health officials puzzled when he warned that people ill with the coronavirus should stay away from painkillers like ibuprofen and aspirin . He said such nonsteroidal anti - inflammatories , or Nsaids , could aggravate symptoms of the coronavirus , and suggested that people take acetaminophen instead . Because the coronavirus is a new pathogen , there is not a lot known on how patients respond to common medications , but other experts pushed back on the French minister \u2019s warning . \u201c It \u2019s all anecdote , and fake news off the anecdotes , \u201d said Dr. Garret FitzGerald , chair of the department of pharmacology at the Perelman School of Medicine at the University of Pennsylvania . The World Health Organization has said that it is aware of no research showing that ibuprofen should not be taken by patients with Covid-19 , and the F.D.A. said it was investigating the issue further and would provide more information when it becomes available . Read MoreIs ibuprofen really risky for coronavirus patients ?", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I heard ibuprofen does n\u2019t work . Is that true ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The health minister of France , Olivier V\u00e9ran , recently left global health officials puzzled when he warned that people ill with the coronavirus should stay away from painkillers like ibuprofen and aspirin . He said such nonsteroidal anti - inflammatories , or Nsaids , could aggravate symptoms of the coronavirus , and suggested that people take acetaminophen instead . Because the coronavirus is a new pathogen , there is not a lot known on how patients respond to common medications , but other experts pushed back on the French minister \u2019s warning . \u201c It \u2019s all anecdote , and fake news off the anecdotes , \u201d said Dr. Garret FitzGerald , chair of the department of pharmacology at the Perelman School of Medicine at the University of Pennsylvania . The World Health Organization has said that it is aware of no research showing that ibuprofen should not be taken by patients with Covid-19 , and the F.D.A. said it was investigating the issue further and would provide more information when it becomes available . Read MoreIs ibuprofen really risky for coronavirus patients ?", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467411, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6ac8-7085-11ea-b602-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6af0-7085-11ea-ba40-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6b22-7085-11ea-9c76-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How long can the virus live on a doorknob ? On cash ? On my keyboard ?", "answerText": "The coronavirus can live up to 72 hours on some surfaces , like plastic and steel , according to a recent study . It can survive on cardboard for up to 24 hours .    The good news is that coronaviruses are easy to destroy . A disinfectant on a surface will render it harmless , according to Gary Whittaker , a professor of virology at the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine . Although the W.H.O. has not said that cash transmits the virus , the organization said in a statement that \u201c it is good hygiene practice to wash your hands after handling money , especially if eating or handling food . \u201d Are you sensing a theme ? Wash your hands after touching almost anything , especially if it \u2019s a surface outside your home .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How long can the virus live on a doorknob ? On cash ? On my keyboard ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The coronavirus can live up to 72 hours on some surfaces , like plastic and steel , according to a recent study . It can survive on cardboard for up to 24 hours .   The good news is that coronaviruses are easy to destroy . A disinfectant on a surface will render it harmless , according to Gary Whittaker , a professor of virology at the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine . Although the W.H.O. has not said that cash transmits the virus , the organization said in a statement that \u201c it is good hygiene practice to wash your hands after handling money , especially if eating or handling food . \u201dAre you sensing a theme ? Wash your hands after touching almost anything , especially if it \u2019s a surface outside your home .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467427, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6b68-7085-11ea-b31a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6b90-7085-11ea-800c-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6bc2-7085-11ea-b2ea-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can the coronavirus live on my clothes ?", "answerText": "Yes , but a different question is what you should do about it . A virus tends to live longer on some nonporous surfaces , like steel or plastic , as compared to fabrics like cotton or leather . But after numerous people who attended a Buddhist temple in Hong Kong fell ill , health workers did find coronavirus on the cloth covers of prayer books , among other items . It \u2019s probably not worth looking up stats and studies about every kind of surface in your life . The takeaway is the same : Disinfect surfaces that are touched a lot and wash your hands after touching anything , and especially before touching your face or eating . ( Two Broadway composers even wrote you a song to sing while you wash ) .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can the coronavirus live on my clothes ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Yes , but a different question is what you should do about it . A virus tends to live longer on some nonporous surfaces , like steel or plastic , as compared to fabrics like cotton or leather . But after numerous people who attended a Buddhist temple in Hong Kong fell ill , health workers did find coronavirus on the cloth covers of prayer books , among other items . It \u2019s probably not worth looking up stats and studies about every kind of surface in your life . The takeaway is the same : Disinfect surfaces that are touched a lot and wash your hands after touching anything , and especially before touching your face or eating . ( Two Broadway composers even wrote you a song to sing while you wash ) .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467442, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6bfe-7085-11ea-b977-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6c26-7085-11ea-8850-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6c58-7085-11ea-a956-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Can I still travel ?", "answerText": "Depending on where you want to go , not easily . In March , as more and more governments around the world hoped to slow the spread of the coronavirus , they began to impose travel restrictions and even close their borders . In the United States , President Trump has said he is considering some restrictions on domestic travel . ( The military has curtailed domestic travel for service members and their families.)And if you do go anywhere , remember to practice social distancing : stay away from groups and keep at least six feet of distance between you and other people . Read More                Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Can I still travel ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Depending on where you want to go , not easily . In March , as more and more governments around the world hoped to slow the spread of the coronavirus , they began to impose travel restrictions and even close their borders . In the United States , President Trump has said he is considering some restrictions on domestic travel . ( The military has curtailed domestic travel for service members and their families.)And if you do go anywhere , remember to practice social distancing : stay away from groups and keep at least six feet of distance between you and other people . Read More               Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467457, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6c94-7085-11ea-8eab-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6cc6-7085-11ea-b91b-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6cee-7085-11ea-b19e-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I do n't mind being alone , but I 'd like to do it somewhere else . Is it possible to road trip responsibly ?", "answerText": "People around the United States are being told to stay home , but you might still need to make a road trip , whether to care for a loved one or for work . If so , follow a general rule : \u201c Do n\u2019t go far , stay in your car , \u201d said Robert Sinclair Jr. , a Northeast regional spokesman for AAA.Mr . Sinclair offered other advice . When pumping gas , sanitize your hands after replacing the pump and before you touch the car door handle , steering wheel and any other part of the vehicle . If an attendant pumped the gas for you , sanitize your credit card after it is handed back to you . Minimize bathroom breaks as much as possible . While this advice goes against AAA \u2019s general advice to take a break every 100 miles , Mr. Sinclair said drivers could rest in vehicles at scenic overlooks or in parking lots of rest stops . Otherwise , wash your hands after using a public restroom and before touching your car . And remember : With guidelines on travel changing rapidly state by state , the rules at your starting point may be different than the rules at your destination . Read More                Here \u2019s what else to consider if you \u2019re traveling by car .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I do n't mind being alone , but I 'd like to do it somewhere else . Is it possible to road trip responsibly ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "People around the United States are being told to stay home , but you might still need to make a road trip , whether to care for a loved one or for work . If so , follow a general rule : \u201c Do n\u2019t go far , stay in your car , \u201d said Robert Sinclair Jr. , a Northeast regional spokesman for AAA.Mr . Sinclair offered other advice . When pumping gas , sanitize your hands after replacing the pump and before you touch the car door handle , steering wheel and any other part of the vehicle . If an attendant pumped the gas for you , sanitize your credit card after it is handed back to you . Minimize bathroom breaks as much as possible . While this advice goes against AAA \u2019s general advice to take a break every 100 miles , Mr. Sinclair said drivers could rest in vehicles at scenic overlooks or in parking lots of rest stops . Otherwise , wash your hands after using a public restroom and before touching your car . And remember : With guidelines on travel changing rapidly state by state , the rules at your starting point may be different than the rules at your destination . Read More               Here \u2019s what else to consider if you \u2019re traveling by car .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4674718, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6d28-7085-11ea-a1e5-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6d52-7085-11ea-ae05-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6d86-7085-11ea-a21f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What about a national park ? Can I go off into the wilderness and be alone ?", "answerText": "It \u2019s a tempting idea , is n\u2019t it ? To explore a national park and be away from other people . Unfortunately , it was also a popular idea . As millions of Americans were asked to stay at home , so many of them decamped to national parks that in mid - March the National Park Service ordered three of the busiest \u2014 Yellowstone , Grand Teton and the Great Smoky Mountains \u2014 to close because of congestion .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What about a national park ? Can I go off into the wilderness and be alone ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "It \u2019s a tempting idea , is n\u2019t it ? To explore a national park and be away from other people . Unfortunately , it was also a popular idea . As millions of Americans were asked to stay at home , so many of them decamped to national parks that in mid - March the National Park Service ordered three of the busiest \u2014 Yellowstone , Grand Teton and the Great Smoky Mountains \u2014 to close because of congestion .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4674869, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6db6-7085-11ea-a728-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6de8-7085-11ea-a854-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6e10-7085-11ea-8cc6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What about my summer vacation ? Should I cancel that ?", "answerText": "No one really knows what the course of the outbreak will be . Some airlines have already announced cuts through May , and President Trump has mentioned isolation measures lasting through July or August . The prevailing optimistic guess among experts for when the outbreak will abate hovers at about two months .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What about my summer vacation ? Should I cancel that ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "No one really knows what the course of the outbreak will be . Some airlines have already announced cuts through May , and President Trump has mentioned isolation measures lasting through July or August . The prevailing optimistic guess among experts for when the outbreak will abate hovers at about two months .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467503, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6e62-7085-11ea-83f8-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6e92-7085-11ea-94d4-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6eba-7085-11ea-84a6-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "My plans got derailed . Can I get a refund ?", "answerText": "With airlines cutting trans - Atlantic flights and cruise lines canceling sailings , travel conditions and refund policies are changing daily . Keep an eye on social media and official communications from your airline , hotel , cruise or wherever you booked to stay up to date with any changes to refund policies . And expect long wait times if you do need to contact a company . Read More                Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "My plans got derailed . Can I get a refund ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "With airlines cutting trans - Atlantic flights and cruise lines canceling sailings , travel conditions and refund policies are changing daily . Keep an eye on social media and official communications from your airline , hotel , cruise or wherever you booked to stay up to date with any changes to refund policies . And expect long wait times if you do need to contact a company . Read More               Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467519, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6f00-7085-11ea-ab96-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6f34-7085-11ea-8466-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b6f5a-7085-11ea-87dd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "If I cancel my flight , will I get my money back ?", "answerText": "You might ! Typically , you would have to at least pay a cancellation fee or booking penalty if you did not buy a fully refundable ticket , which is usually more expensive . But many airlines , including Delta , United and American , are loosening their booking policies and suspending cancellation or rescheduling fees . Read More                Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "If I cancel my flight , will I get my money back ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "You might ! Typically , you would have to at least pay a cancellation fee or booking penalty if you did not buy a fully refundable ticket , which is usually more expensive . But many airlines , including Delta , United and American , are loosening their booking policies and suspending cancellation or rescheduling fees . Read More               Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467535, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b6f9e-7085-11ea-8a06-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b6fd2-7085-11ea-b008-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b7006-7085-11ea-afc1-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What about travel insurance ?", "answerText": "Typically , insurance companies will cover disrupted or canceled trips only under very specific circumstances . But if you purchased cancel - for - any - reason insurance for your trip , there \u2019s a good chance you will get a good share of your money back . Be sure to read the fine print on your coverage before speaking with a representative . Read More                Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What about travel insurance ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Typically , insurance companies will cover disrupted or canceled trips only under very specific circumstances . But if you purchased cancel - for - any - reason insurance for your trip , there \u2019s a good chance you will get a good share of your money back . Be sure to read the fine print on your coverage before speaking with a representative . Read More               Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467552, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b704a-7085-11ea-b03a-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b707a-7085-11ea-b013-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b70a4-7085-11ea-8cbf-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I ca n\u2019t get my airline on the phone . What should I do ?", "answerText": "\u201c Obviously , the 800 numbers are overwhelmed , \u201d said Michael Holtz , the founder and chief executive of SmartFlyer , a luxury travel agency . Many airlines in the United States have informed travelers that they could expect longer wait times to speak to a customer service agent . Some have redirected callers to their websites and their apps , or asked travelers to leave their contact information for an agent . Contacting an airline via social media platforms like Twitter and Facebook may be your best option right now . \u201c My advice is to use technology , \u201d he said . Read More                Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I ca n\u2019t get my airline on the phone . What should I do ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "\u201c Obviously , the 800 numbers are overwhelmed , \u201d said Michael Holtz , the founder and chief executive of SmartFlyer , a luxury travel agency . Many airlines in the United States have informed travelers that they could expect longer wait times to speak to a customer service agent . Some have redirected callers to their websites and their apps , or asked travelers to leave their contact information for an agent . Contacting an airline via social media platforms like Twitter and Facebook may be your best option right now . \u201cMy advice is to use technology , \u201d he said . Read More               Here are more answers to questions about travel .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4675672, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b70e2-7085-11ea-9446-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b711c-7085-11ea-bc89-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b7146-7085-11ea-9b0f-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "China seems to be getting back to normal life . How long will that take in the U.S. ?", "answerText": "No one knows . China began taking draconian measures to control the coronavirus in late January , and it was not until almost two months later that it reported no new local infections . South Korea did not lock down cities in the same way , but was extremely fast to test people , trace their contacts and quarantine infected people . And although China and South Korea have demonstrated that , with drastic actions , the virus can be brought under control , there is no guarantee it wo n\u2019t resurge as their economies restart . The U.S. has taken a much more piecemeal approach to confronting the virus . To repeat the success of other countries , experts say , it will take extraordinary coordination and money from the government , and extraordinary trust and cooperation from citizens .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "China seems to be getting back to normal life . How long will that take in the U.S. ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "No one knows . China began taking draconian measures to control the coronavirus in late January , and it was not until almost two months later that it reported no new local infections . South Korea did not lock down cities in the same way , but was extremely fast to test people , trace their contacts and quarantine infected people . And although China and South Korea have demonstrated that , with drastic actions , the virus can be brought under control , there is no guarantee it wo n\u2019t resurge as their economies restart . The U.S. has taken a much more piecemeal approach to confronting the virus . To repeat the success of other countries , experts say , it will take extraordinary coordination and money from the government , and extraordinary trust and cooperation from citizens .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467584, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b7194-7085-11ea-82bf-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b71d0-7085-11ea-aec5-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b71f8-7085-11ea-9b3c-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "How is this going to affect the 2020 election ?", "answerText": "Several states have already postponed their primaries . Officials in states that are going ahead with primaries have been trying to emphasize the new basics of voting hygiene , like using hand sanitizer at polling stations . And though the general election has yet to begin , it is already being profoundly shaped by the coronavirus , which has become the central issue between President Trump and the two major Democratic candidates , former Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr. and Senator Bernie Sanders of Vermont . The pandemic \u2019s effects on the economy have challenged Mr. Trump \u2019s core message , that Americans are better off than before he took office . Mr. Biden has proposed a detailed plan for hospitals and research , echoing the language of presidents in past crises . He and Mr. Sanders curtailed their travel and canceled large gatherings like rallies . It would be enormously difficult to cancel or postpone the November general election , though . Read MoreHere \u2019s more about holding an election in a crisis .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "How is this going to affect the 2020 election ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Several states have already postponed their primaries . Officials in states that are going ahead with primaries have been trying to emphasize the new basics of voting hygiene , like using hand sanitizer at polling stations . And though the general election has yet to begin , it is already being profoundly shaped by the coronavirus , which has become the central issue between President Trump and the two major Democratic candidates , former Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr. and Senator Bernie Sanders of Vermont . The pandemic \u2019s effects on the economy have challenged Mr. Trump \u2019s core message , that Americans are better off than before he took office . Mr. Biden has proposed a detailed plan for hospitals and research , echoing the language of presidents in past crises . He and Mr. Sanders curtailed their travel and canceled large gatherings like rallies . It would be enormously difficult to cancel or postpone the November general election , though . Read MoreHere \u2019s more about holding an election in a crisis .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4676008, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b7234-7085-11ea-9c1d-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b7266-7085-11ea-92a1-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b728c-7085-11ea-9b09-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What is the U.S. government doing to help the economy ?", "answerText": "On March 27 , Congress passed a $ 2 trillion rescue package , the largest economic stimulus measure in modern history , to help the people , businesses and industries affected by the coronavirus outbreak . In its sheer scope and size , the aid plan is unprecedented and touches on every facet of American life . Its components include stimulus payments to individuals , expanded unemployment coverage that includes the self - employed , student loan changes and much more . Read MoreRead about the legislation here .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What is the U.S. government doing to help the economy ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "On March 27 , Congress passed a $ 2 trillion rescue package , the largest economic stimulus measure in modern history , to help the people , businesses and industries affected by the coronavirus outbreak . In its sheer scope and size , the aid plan is unprecedented and touches on every facet of American life . Its components include stimulus payments to individuals , expanded unemployment coverage that includes the self - employed , student loan changes and much more . Read MoreRead about the legislation here .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467618, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b72de-7085-11ea-ac71-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b7310-7085-11ea-aa75-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b7342-7085-11ea-9ea2-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What are some of the details of the stimulus package ?", "answerText": "The legislation would send direct payments of $ 1,200 to millions of Americans , including those earning up to $ 75,000 , and an additional $ 500 per child . It expands jobless aid , providing an additional 13 weeks and a four - month enhancement of benefits , and extends the payments for the first time to freelancers and gig workers . The measure would also offer $ 377 billion in federally guaranteed loans to small businesses and establish a $ 500 billion government lending program for distressed companies reeling from the impact of the crisis , including allowing the administration the ability to take equity stakes in airlines that received aid to help compensate taxpayers . It would also send $ 100 billion to hospitals on the front lines of the pandemic . Read MoreHere \u2019s a F.A.Q. on stimulus checks , unemployment aid and other details of the stimulus plan .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What are some of the details of the stimulus package ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The legislation would send direct payments of $ 1,200 to millions of Americans , including those earning up to $ 75,000 , and an additional $ 500 per child . It expands jobless aid , providing an additional 13 weeks and a four - month enhancement of benefits , and extends the payments for the first time to freelancers and gig workers . The measure would also offer $ 377 billion in federally guaranteed loans to small businesses and establish a $ 500 billion government lending program for distressed companies reeling from the impact of the crisis , including allowing the administration the ability to take equity stakes in airlines that received aid to help compensate taxpayers . It would also send $ 100 billion to hospitals on the front lines of the pandemic . Read MoreHere \u2019s a F.A.Q. on stimulus checks , unemployment aid and other details of the stimulus plan .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467635, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b7388-7085-11ea-8b35-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b73ba-7085-11ea-825a-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b73e2-7085-11ea-90b4-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "I \u2019 ve seen movies about quarantines . How far can the government go ?", "answerText": "The federal government can impose quarantines under the Public Health Service Act to prevent the spread of communicable disease into the United States or between states . They \u2019re considered a measure of last resort when there \u2019s no other way to stop the spread of a deadly disease . On the state and local level , the laws vary depending on the region . Still , the U.S. government does n\u2019t have the authority to impose a quarantine as sweeping as China , which confined some 70 million people in the largest effort in history . In the U.S. , quarantines have been very rare . The last one was in the 1960s against a suspected smallpox outbreak . Health warnings are more common , like in 2016 when the C.D.C. advised pregnant women to avoid Southern Florida during an outbreak of the Zika virus . Read More                Learn about this measure of last resort .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "I \u2019ve seen movies about quarantines . How far can the government go ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "The federal government can impose quarantines under the Public Health Service Act to prevent the spread of communicable disease into the United States or between states . They \u2019re considered a measure of last resort when there \u2019s no other way to stop the spread of a deadly disease . On the state and local level , the laws vary depending on the region . Still , the U.S. government does n\u2019t have the authority to impose a quarantine as sweeping as China , which confined some 70 million people in the largest effort in history . In the U.S. , quarantines have been very rare . The last one was in the 1960s against a suspected smallpox outbreak . Health warnings are more common , like in 2016 when the C.D.C. advised pregnant women to avoid Southern Florida during an outbreak of the Zika virus . Read More               Learn about this measure of last resort .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.46765, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b741e-7085-11ea-b677-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b7450-7085-11ea-9214-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b7478-7085-11ea-b006-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Why is every country responding so differently ?", "answerText": "A lot has to do with politics and history . While some places , like Hong Kong , have had extensive experience with serious outbreaks and quickly put in place a plan to contain the virus , others were slower to react and failed to take the outbreak seriously enough , according to the W.H.O. That \u2019s contributed to the lack of a united response . While the W.H.O. is supposed to coordinate the global response to epidemics , the group , a U.N. agency , does n\u2019t have the authority to force countries to follow its plan . Culture and government also play a role . Chinese citizens responded quickly to aggressive restrictions put in place by their authoritarian government , while Italians were n\u2019t initially as compliant .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Why is every country responding so differently ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "A lot has to do with politics and history . While some places , like Hong Kong , have had extensive experience with serious outbreaks and quickly put in place a plan to contain the virus , others were slower to react and failed to take the outbreak seriously enough , according to the W.H.O. That \u2019s contributed to the lack of a united response . While the W.H.O. is supposed to coordinate the global response to epidemics , the group , a U.N. agency , does n\u2019t have the authority to force countries to follow its plan . Culture and government also play a role . Chinese citizens responded quickly to aggressive restrictions put in place by their authoritarian government , while Italians were n\u2019t initially as compliant .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.467666, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b74c8-7085-11ea-9c12-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b74f0-7085-11ea-9523-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b7522-7085-11ea-98cd-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Is there a country that \u2019s really handled this well ?", "answerText": "Governments worldwide have made major mistakes in trying to contain the outbreak . But as the virus spreads , South Korea , Singapore and China have been more effective than others at bringing it under control . South Korea has aggressively monitored infections , such as by checking the body temperatures of all incoming and outgoing passengers at train stations and other places . Officials operate drive - through testing centers and send out mobile phone alerts to citizens when new cases are reported in their districts . Singapore , which has focused on early diagnosis , isolation and contact tracing , has also seen its rate of new cases drop . In China , new reported infections were cut to just 24 in a recent headcount from more than 3,500 a day in late January . In addition to strict travel limitations , Chinese people are required to wear masks outdoors and have their temperatures checked at the doors of office buildings , stores , restaurants , hotels , apartments and public transit stations .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Is there a country that \u2019s really handled this well ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Governments worldwide have made major mistakes in trying to contain the outbreak . But as the virus spreads , South Korea , Singapore and China have been more effective than others at bringing it under control . South Korea has aggressively monitored infections , such as by checking the body temperatures of all incoming and outgoing passengers at train stations and other places . Officials operate drive - through testing centers and send out mobile phone alerts to citizens when new cases are reported in their districts . Singapore , which has focused on early diagnosis , isolation and contact tracing , has also seen its rate of new cases drop . In China , new reported infections were cut to just 24 in a recent headcount from more than 3,500 a day in late January . In addition to strict travel limitations , Chinese people are required to wear masks outdoors and have their temperatures checked at the doors of office buildings , stores , restaurants , hotels , apartments and public transit stations .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4676821, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b755e-7085-11ea-84c0-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b7590-7085-11ea-b5d3-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b75b8-7085-11ea-979d-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "Has anyone in the government gotten sick ?", "answerText": "Around the world , a number of senior officials from Iran to Australia have contracted the virus . The British prime minister , Boris Johnson , announced on March 27 that he tested positive . Justin Trudeau , the Canadian prime minister , said he was putting himself in isolation after his wife tested positive . President Trump tested negative for the coronavirus , officials said . Mr. Trump had been in contact with two Brazilian officials who tested positive days after meeting him in Florida . Mayor Francis Suarez of Miami , who also met the Brazilian delegation , said he tested positive . At least three members of Congress have tested positive for the coronavirus , including Senator Rand Paul .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "Has anyone in the government gotten sick ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "Around the world , a number of senior officials from Iran to Australia have contracted the virus . The British prime minister , Boris Johnson , announced on March 27 that he tested positive . Justin Trudeau , the Canadian prime minister , said he was putting himself in isolation after his wife tested positive . President Trump tested negative for the coronavirus , officials said . Mr. Trump had been in contact with two Brazilian officials who tested positive days after meeting him in Florida . Mayor Francis Suarez of Miami , who also met the Brazilian delegation , said he tested positive . At least three members of Congress have tested positive for the coronavirus , including Senator Rand Paul .", "answerLinks": {}}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/world/coronavirus-tips-advice.html", "sourceName": "NYTimes", "dateScraped": 1585352981.4676979, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1585195200.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "a08b75fe-7085-11ea-8423-8c85901aafa7", "answerUUID": "a08b7630-7085-11ea-a415-8c85901aafa7", "exampleUUID": "a08b7662-7085-11ea-aa84-8c85901aafa7", "questionText": "What if Congress gets sick ?", "answerText": "It \u2019s not clear , and keeping Congress at work in the Capitol may prove untenable , especially if more lawmakers fall ill or as staff and services dwindle . During the Cold War and after Sept. 11 , 2001 , the government devised emergency plans to protect government officials , like a nuclear bunker for Congress in West Virginia , now a tourist attraction . Those plans relied on the ability to gather lawmakers in a safe place together , however \u2014 a hazard during a pandemic . \" There 's no serious effort to grapple with what could happen in the event of a major catastrophe , \" said Norm Ornstein , a resident scholar at the conservative American Enterprise Institute who pushed for plans in the wake of Sept. 11 . He said that a bill to allow remote voting during a national crisis , put forward by Senators Rob Portman and Richard Durbin , was \" a good start . \" So far , congressional leaders have resisted calls for remote voting , calling it a bad precedent and saying they need to address the current crisis . They have instead looked for ways to practice social distancing within the Capitol . \" There 's reason to be wary about a virtual Congress , \" Mr. Ornstein said , like ensuring cybersecurity and that Americans can still see and hear lawmakers at work . But he added that House and Senate leaders , through legislation or rule changes , could create the capacity for remote voting only in the most extreme circumstances , such as when many members are incapacitated or transportation to the Capitol or an alternate meeting place becomes impossible .", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {"original_questionText": "What if Congress gets sick ?", "questionLinks": {}, "original_answerText": "It \u2019s not clear , and keeping Congress at work in the Capitol may prove untenable , especially if more lawmakers fall ill or as staff and services dwindle . During the Cold War and after Sept. 11 , 2001 , the government devised emergency plans to protect government officials , like a nuclear bunker for Congress in West Virginia , now a tourist attraction . Those plans relied on the ability to gather lawmakers in a safe place together , however \u2014 a hazard during a pandemic . \" There 's no serious effort to grapple with what could happen in the event of a major catastrophe , \" said Norm Ornstein , a resident scholar at the conservative American Enterprise Institute who pushed for plans in the wake of Sept. 11 . He said that a bill to allow remote voting during a national crisis , put forward by Senators Rob Portman and Richard Durbin , was \" a good start . \"So far , congressional leaders have resisted calls for remote voting , calling it a bad precedent and saying they need to address the current crisis . They have instead looked for ways to practice social distancing within the Capitol . \" There 's reason to be wary about a virtual Congress , \" Mr. Ornstein said , like ensuring cybersecurity and that Americans can still see and hear lawmakers at work . But he added that House and Senate leaders , through legislation or rule changes , could create the capacity for remote voting only in the most extreme circumstances , such as when many members are incapacitated or transportation to the Capitol or an alternate meeting place becomes impossible .", "answerLinks": {}}}
